(Sheldon:)-So you betrayed me.
-No.
(Penny:)It wasn't a betrayal.
It was more of a, I can't afford
any more points on my license.
(Penny:)I already have to buy my insurance
from this place in the Cayman Islands.
(Sheldon:)But the only reason
I was driving your car...
(Sheldon:)...was because you were in distress,
and I was rescuing you.
Yes. And look, now you have a photo
to remember that heroic day.
(Leonard:)It's not that big a deal.
(Leonard:)You just go down to the court on Thursday,
and you pay the fine.
(Sheldon:)I'm not going to pay a fine.
That would imply I'm guilty.
(Howard:)You are guilty.
[LAW & ORDER'S "THE CLANG"
PLAYS OVER SPEAKER]
(Howard:)-That one I liked.
-Yeah.
(Sheldon:)I am not guilty.
I only have a learner's permit.
(Sheldon:)Penny was the teacher.
When the light turned yellow...
...she said, "Go, go, go,"
so I went, went, went.
(Penny:)Sheldon, I'm sorry. I'll be happy
to reimburse you for the fine.
(Penny:)You know, as soon as I get a part
in a movie or my own TV series.
(Sheldon:)You don't need to reimburse me.
I'm not paying.
(Sheldon:)On Thursday, I will have my day in court,
and justice will be done.